<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView2"
        android:layout_width="368dp"
        android:layout_height="90dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="21dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="21dp"
        android:text="What can we do about Climate Change?"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textSize="33sp"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />


    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_marginStart="20dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="100dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="20dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">


        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="There are many things you can do to take action about climate change. Here are 3 ways you can help the world. \n\n     1) Take public transport. Public transport is a cheap way of getting around, and it is not very slow either. Petrol and Diesel cost a lot, and they also release many greenhouse gases when burned in an engine. Even though public transport releases more greenhouse gases than private transport, much more people can travel in it, so it is actually much more efficient. \n\n Extension on 1: Cycle when you can. After all, engines aren’t made to spin. Engines are made to generate heat and boil petrol or diesel, and it is just a side effect that it can be used, however inefficiently, to spin something. It’s better to cycle with a bicycle. At least that is made to spin and move, unlike an engine, and is much better for the environment. It is also a form of exercise so you can also be more fit. \n\n 2) Reduce emissions. Buying things and using plastic bags and disposable utensils causes there to be lot of plastic waste each year, and you can do your part to save the environment. If plastic is burnt, that releases greenhouse gases. If it is dumped into the ocean, the sea will be more polluted and marine animals can die. If left to decompose, that will take hundreds of years, and even then, they decompose into microplastics which are harmful in a different way. Big plastics choke animals or trap them, small plastics are like viruses and bacteria. \n\n Extension on 2: Not buying things reduces the demand for them, so there may be less companies making them because an excess of supply would be useless. Cutting prices will have a limit. Eventually, we can manufacture less plastics, and manufacturing usually releases greenhouse gases, so we will be helping the environment. This also applies to all other products, including treated water and in some countries, even tap water. Using a mug to brush your teeth can help the environment. \n\n Further Extension on 2: Use cleaner less electricity. Electricity can come from many sources, some harming the environment and releasing greenhouse gases, and some actually reducing the temperature of the earth under special circumstances! Try to use energy from renewable sources, like wind, solar, geothermal, hydroelectric and tidal. Nuclear energy also has no emissions, although it has some risks. Try to get your electricity from a utility company that generates a huge part of its energy with renewable sources or nuclear power. Using less electricity also has many benefits. You save on electricity bills, the company can relax and does not have to worry too much about not providing enough electricity, and it’s better for the environment. After all, renewable energy and nuclear power can only generate so much electricity. We also need to cut down on our electricity usage. Simple things like switching off the water heater and lights when not in use and shutting down your computer when not going to be used can make a huge difference if everyone did so. This brings us to the third way of stopping climate change. \n\n     3) Spread the word. This is the most important thing to do. The more people know about this and care about this, the more people will cooperate and the more chance there is to make a very significant change. Each person might not be able to contribute much, but if everyone contributes, then the world can be saved. The ways mentioned earlier require people to cooperate. Imagine taking a bus, but actually the bus has only you and the driver in it. Then it would still be better for the environment to take private transport. If only you decided not to use reusable cutlery, it will not make much of a difference.  " />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>




</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>